Guide to the Organization of Staff Analysts Records WAG.191
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Files
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Personnel Examiners Council, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Predecessor Organizations: Professional Personnel Association, Personnel Examiners Council, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Prep Course: Topics in Organizational Research for Associate Staff Analysts, undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Press Clippings, 1960s (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Press Clippings, 1970s (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Press Clippings, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Press Clippings, 1990s (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Press Clippings, 2000s (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Press Clippings, undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Privatization, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Procedures, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Procedures, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Procedures, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Profit and Loss Statements/Operating Expenses, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Proposal to Establish a Safety and Health Program in OSA, Jun 6, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Provisionals, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - PICA (Psychotropic, Injectable, Chemotherapy, and Asthma) Prescription Benefits Program, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Public Health: Proposal on Titles, undated (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Quality of Work Life Program: Labor Relations Unions Employee Recognition Location Awards Ceremony, Jul 28, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Quality of Work Life Program, Office of the Controller: Tenth Annual Employee Recognition Ceremony, Nov 13, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Quality of Work Life Program, Office of the Controller: Eleventh Annual Employee Recognition Ceremony, Dec 6, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Queens College: Worker Education Program, undated (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Rebroadbanding of Staff Analysis and Education Analysis Occupational Groups, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Redeployment Plan, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Regarding the Use of the I in 3 Rule, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reorganization Plan: "The members would like to know", 1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Salary Adjustment Plan: City of New York, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sicular, Roy (Petitioner) and Bob Croghan, President, OSA (Respondent): Improper Practice Petition and related materials, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Activists' Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Activists' List, 1977-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Advanced Wages Receipts, 1970-1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Chapter Index and related materials, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Finance Committee, 1969, 1974, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): General, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): General, 1970s (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): General, 1980s (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): General, 1990s (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Local 371 Activists' Directory, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Local 371 Campaign for Analysts, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Local 371 Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Local 371 HRA Chapter By-Laws (revised), Mar 9, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Organizing Campaign Flyers, Department of Welfare, 1966-1968 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Social Services Employees Union (SSEU): Welfare Plan, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Solidarity with Local 32B-32JStrikers, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Stabilization Fund: Projections through FY 2005, Mar 13, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Staff Analysis Occupational Group (253): Position Postings, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - State of New York Public Employment Relations Board Case No. U-7479, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Stipulation and Order Index No. 6703/84: Arthur Cheliotes, President, Communication Workers of America v. City of NY, Jun 1992 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Stipulation of Settlement and Memorandum of Understanding and "Supplemental Agreement to the Staff Analysts 1995-2000 Unit Agreement" (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Supervising Systems Analysts: "Bob's [Croghan] Book", 2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Supervising Systems Analysts: Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC) "Booklet II", 2000 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Survey of Members: Various Agencies, undated (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Systems Analysts: Title Series as of March 4, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - 30th Anniversary Celebration, Oct 19, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - 30th Anniversary Celebration: correspondence, lists and other related materials, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - 30th Anniversary Celebration: Program Journal Ad Orders, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Transport Security Administration and Bob Marchetta: Research for Bob Croghan, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Transport Workers Union Local 100: 3rd Annual James Connolly/ Mike Quill Celebration "Irish Night", Mar 14, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Union Affiliations of OSA, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Unionist Articles, 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Unionization of All Staff and Associate Staff Analysts (Mayoral Agencies and Offices of Elected Officials): Draft, Dec 31, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - UAW: Constitution of the International Union/United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America UAW (including copy of 1981 Constitution of the International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 1986 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Unmatched List of Analysts Report, Mar 5, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Voice, 1981-1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Wage Issues, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Fund: Amivest Capital Management Presentation, Dec 8, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Welfare Fund: Communication Workers of America (CWA) Local 1180 Reports, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Welfare Fund: Deferred Compensation Program Highlights from T. Rowe Price, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Fund: Dental Program, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Welfare Fund: Financial Materials, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Welfare Fund: Financial Statements, Dec 2003 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Welfare Fund: Financials, Croghan notes, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Welfare Fund: General, 2003 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Welfare Fund: GHI Directory, undated (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Welfare Fund: GHI Fiscal Year 2005 Renewal, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Welfare Fund: GHI/Value Options Mental Health/Clinical Dependency Proposal, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Welfare Fund: Group Life and Disability Insurance Proposal from Prudential, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Welfare Fund: Group LTD (Disability) Insurance, undated (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Welfare Fund: H & R Phillips "broker-of-record", 1989 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Welfare Fund: Labor Management Health Insurance Policy Committee, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Welfare Fund: Life Insurance, Prudential Materials for Employees, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Welfare Fund: Magellan Mental Health/Chemical Dependency Presentation, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Welfare Fund: "Management Benefits Voice", Jun 30, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Welfare Fund: "Management Benefits Voice", Winter 2004 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Welfare Fund: Mental Health/Chemical Dependency Proposal Rating Sheet, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Welfare Fund: National Vision Administrators Vision Presentation Sections I and II, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Welfare Fund: National Vision Administrators Vision Presentation Section III, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Fund: National Vision Administrators Vision Presentation Sections IV and V, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Welfare Fund: National Vision Administrators Vision Presentation to OSA Meeting, Jan 7, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Welfare Fund: Packet for New OSA Members, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Welfare Fund: Possible Problems with GHI Prescription Reimbursements, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Welfare Fund: Reports, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Welfare Fund: Reports, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Welfare Fund: Request for Proposal (RFP) Evaluation of various group health insurance plans/providers, Jun 10, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Welfare Fund: Reserve Fund - Long Term Investment Project, Mar 11, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Welfare Fund: Supplemental Group Term Life Insurance Program, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Welfare Fund: United Behavioral Health Mental Health/Chemical Dependency Presentation, Jun 10, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Welfare Fund: United Behavioral Health Sample Communications Materials, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Welfare Fund: Vision Care Plan Annual Report, Jan 1, 1994-Dec 31, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Welfare Fund and Educational Fund: Financial Statements, Dec 31, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Welfare Fund Trustees: Minutes, Appeals, Correspondence, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Why Unions… Pamphlets, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Big Meeting, Aug 5, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Coalition Meeting, Feb 20, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Conference and related materials, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): General, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Materials re: welfare reform, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): OSA in-house meeting, Jul 27, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): OSA in-house meeting, Jul 30, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): OSA in-house meeting, Aug 13, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): OSA "WAVE (Workforce Awareness Vigil Engagement) Letter" (107 Sent), Jul 14, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Orientation Manual, [1996] (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Policy and Procedures Manual (Draft), May 21, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Responses to "WAVE (Workforce Awareness Vigil Engagement) Letter", 1998 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Sheila's new list of WEP Connections, Jul 23, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Vigil, Interested Parties, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): Vigil (Red), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): "Welfare, Workfare, and Jobs, An Educator's Guidebook", 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): WAVE (Workforce Awareness Vigil Engagement), Jul 1998-Aug 1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): WAVE (Workforce Awareness Vigil Engagement) Meeting, Jul 7, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Work Experience Program (WEP): WAVE (Workforce Awareness Vigil Engagement) Responses, May 1, 1998-Jul 1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Worksheet for Dues Restructuring, Jul 1, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - www.osaunion.org: guide, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Zip Code Guide, 1975 (?) (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Series III: Agencies
  - Administration for Children's Services (ACS): General, 1999, 2002 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Administration for Children's Services (ACS): Transfer Certification, Dec 2001 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Added Analysts, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agency Shop Fee Procedure, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agency Shop Fee Procedure, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agreement (Executed Copy) Jul 1, 1985-Jun 30, 1987, Feb 23, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agreement (Executed Copy) Jul 1, 1987-Jun 30, 1990, Jun 29, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agreement (Draft and Executed Copy) Jul 1, 1990-Sep 30, 1991, Dec 1992 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agreement (Executed Copy) Oct 1, 1991-Dec 31, 1994, May 1996 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agreement Jan 1, 1995-Dec 31, 1999 (Draft # 2/3), Apr 1999 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Agreement Jan 1, 1995-Dec 31, 1999, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Approval of the 1991-1995 Municipal Coalition Economic Agreement, Apr 1993 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Budget, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Budget, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Coalition of Unions, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Coalition of Unions, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Coalition of Unions, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Coalition of Unions, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Coalition of Unions, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Coalition of Unions, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Collective Bargaining campaign and election, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Contract Negotiations Draft Agreement for Jul 1, 1990-Sep 30, 1991; BOE/NYC School district Agreement Jan 1, 1983-Dec 31, 1985, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Court Cases - BOE v. Public Employment Relations Board (PERB), 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Court Cases - BOE v. PERB, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Court Cases - BOE v. PERB, 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Court Cases - OSA and Michael Mackay v. BOE, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Employee Information System Number of Employees by title code paid on 12-31-96/1-10-97, Jan 27, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Employee Information System Number of Employees by title code paid on 12-31-96/1-10-97, Feb 3, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Managerial/Confidential Exclusions, Complete Copy of the PERB Decision, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Negotiations, 1987-1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Vacancy Announcements (see HHC Layoffs), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Welfare Fund Agreement (Draft), 1985 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Welfare Fund Agreement (Executed Copy), 1987 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Welfare Fund Agreements, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Board of Education (BOE): Welfare Fund Agreements (Executed Copy) Jan 1, 1995-Dec 31, 1999, Jun 14, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW): Bronx Office, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW): General, 1970s-1980s (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Department of Corrections: Civilian-Non-Managerial Time and Leave Manual, Personnel Division, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Department of Design and Construction (DDC): Promotion Lists, 2001-2004 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Department of Environmental Protection (DEP): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Department of Finance: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Department of Finance: Code of Conduct, Jul 26, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Department of Finance: Code of Conduct, Mar 12, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Department of Finance: Employee Disciplinary Manual, 1984 (?) (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Department of Finance: Employee Handbook, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Department of Health (DOH): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Department of Health (DOH): Infection Control Manual (Draft), Jul 31, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Department of Health (DOH): Managerial/Confidential (ZZ), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Department of Homeless Services (DHS): Administrative Manual, Dec 1993 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Department of Homeless Services (DHS): City Council Hearing re: Establishment of this Department, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Department of Homeless Services (DHS): Establishment of Agency, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Department of Homeless Services (DHS): Establishment of Agency; Staff Rosters of Proposed Transferees, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Department of Homeless Services (DHS): Four Shelter Privatization Initiative (contracting out), Oct 1994 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Department of Housing Preservation and Development (HPD): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Department of Housing Preservation and Development (HPD): Notice of Layoffs, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice (DJJ): Agency Lateness Policy, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice (DJJ): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice (DJJ): Managerial/Confidential (ZZ), 1990 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Department of Juvenile Justice (DJJ): Standard of Conduct Effective Oct 15, 1985; Revised Feb 6, 1991 and Oct 28, 1996, 1991, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Department of Mental Health: Excerpts from and summary of Comptroller's Internal Control and Accountability Directive 6, Mar 1, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Department of Mental Health: Executive Orders, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Department of Mental Health: General, 1982-1993 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Department of Mental Health: Personnel and Budget Bulletins, 1985-1993 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Department of Mental Health: Policy and Procedural Notices, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Department of Mental Health: Standards of Conduct, Jul 1987 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Department of Parks and Recreation: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Department of Personnel (DOP): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Department of Personnel (DOP): Management Employee Roster for DSS-Agency Code 069, Jan 15, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Department of Sanitation: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Department of Sanitation: Employee of the Year Award and Unit Citation Ceremony, Jun 4, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Department of Sanitation: Managerial/Confidential (ZZ), 1992 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): Citywide Section 55-a Program (for persons with disabilities), 1997 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): General, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): Managerial/Confidential (ZZ), 1992 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Department of Transportation (DOT): Request for proposals to operate, maintain and privatize the Summons Processing Systems of the New York City Parking Violations Bureau, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Department of Youth Services: Code of Conduct, [1990s ?] (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Fire Department: City of New York and OSA Survey, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): General, undated, 1980, 1992-2003 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): General - Harlem Hospital, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): General - Segundo Ruiz Belvis Diagnostic and Treatment Center, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Layoffs, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Bellevue Hospital Center, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Bellevue Hospital Center, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center (BMHC), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Bronx Municipal Hospital Center (BMHC), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Central Office, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Central Office, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Coler Memorial Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Coler Memorial Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Coney Island Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Coney Island Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Cumberland Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Cumberland Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - East New York Diagnostic and Treatment Center (D & TC), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Elmhurst Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Elmhurst Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Emergency Medical Services (EMS), 1993 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Emergency Medical Services (EMS), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Goldwater Memorial Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Gouverneur Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Gouverneur Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Harlem Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Harlem Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Kings County Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Lincoln Hospital, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Lincoln Hospital, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC): Managerial Analysis Summary - Metropolitan Hospital Center, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 31)